<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wecycle</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyAgkN-hpzsWKExY1_y1iyZLobI2012vi1k</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="settings">Ajustes</string>
    <string name="filter">Filtro</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plástico</string>
    <string name="organic">Orgánico</string>
    <string name="waste">Residuos</string>
    <string name="paper">Papel</string>
    <string name="glass">Vidrio</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">InfoActivity</string>

    <string name="what_is_appcontainer">¿Qué es Wecycle?</string>
    <string name="descriptionAppContainer">Wecycle es una herramienta diseñada para ayudarte a reciclar de manera más eficiente, salvando al medio ambiente y ahorrándote a tí tiempo!</string>
    <string name="DescriptionMap">Encuentra los contenedores de reciclaje más cercanos a tu localización.</string>
    <string name="map">Dónde reciclar</string>
    <string name="filters">No te distraigas</string>
    <string name="DescriptionInfo">Wecycle te enseña todo lo que necesitas saber para ampliar tus conocmientos sobre el reciclaje</string>
    <string name="Info">¿No sabes como reciclar?</string>
    <string name="DescriptionFilters">Usa los filtros customizables y ajustes que se adaptan a tus necesidades y preferencias</string>
    <string name="selectall">Seleccionar todo</string>
    <string name="which_where"><![CDATA[Which & Where]]></string>
    <string name="info_plastic1">- <b>Contenedores de plástico:</b> any basic plastic packaging, seran wrap, plastic bottles, PET, PVC&#8230;\n- <b>Contenedores de metal:</b> containers like tuna tins or aluminium foil have to be clean before putting them into the recycling.
    </string>
    <string name="info_plastic2">- <b>Bolsas de plástico:</b> they can be reused many times, but when you are finished with them, recycle them in the plastic bins.\n- <b>Envases o Tetrabriks:</b> packaging used for milk, juice, tomato sauce and more.
        </string>
    <string name="info_paper">- <b>Papel:</b> standard office papers, magazines, newspapers&#8230;\n- <b>Cartón:</b> cardboard boxes, cereal boxes and the like. Not milk and juice boxes, those go in the plastic bins.\n- <b>Otros</b>: comics, paper or cardboard packaging, brochures, envelopes, advertising, paper sheets&#8230;
    </string>
    <string name="info_glass">- <b>Vidrio:</b> glass bottles, jars and containers. Do not include the metal lids to jars or the bottle caps. Do not throw fluorescents, light bulbs, mirrors, glasses, plates or broken ashtrays. Lightbulbs and such can be dropped off at specific stores.\n- <b>Cosmeticos:</b> empty perfume and cosmetic bottles.</string>
    <string name="info_organic">- <b>Basura organica:</b> leftover fruit and vegetables, scraps of meat and fish, shells of eggs, nuts, seafood. Also coffee grounds, teas, matches, sawdust.\n- <b>Dirty paper:</b> you can also deposit dirty kitchen paper, used napkins and oil stained cardboard.</string>
    <string name="info_waste">- <b>No organico: </b>diapers, pads, tampons, wet wipes, cigarette butts, dust, animal feces, litter sand, hair and pet fur, surgical face masks.</string>


</resources>
