<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE resources [
    <!ENTITY appname "Wecycle">
    ]>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyAgkN-hpzsWKExY1_y1iyZLobI2012vi1k</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">InfoActivity</string>
    <string name="what_is_appcontainer">Welcome to &appname;</string>
    <string name="descriptionAppContainer">&appname; is a tool that helps you recycle in a more efficient way, saving the environment while saving you time!</string>
    <string name="DescriptionMap">Wecycle\'s map helps you locate the closest recycling containers to your current location</string>
    <string name="map">Where to recycle</string>
    <string name="filters">Don\'t get distracted</string>
    <string name="DescriptionInfo">Wecycle teaches you everything you need to broaden your knowledge on recycling</string>
    <string name="Info">Don\'t know how it works?</string>
    <string name="DescriptionFilters">Use the customizable filters and settings to adapt the search to your needs and preferences</string>
    <string name="selectall">Select All</string>
    <string name="which_where"><![CDATA[Which & Where]]></string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="glass">Glass</string>
    <string name="organic">Organic</string>
    <string name="waste">Waste</string>
    <string name="info_plastic1">- <b>Plastic containers:</b> any basic plastic packaging, seran wrap, plastic bottles, PET, PVC&#8230;\n- <b>Metal containers:</b> containers like tuna tins or aluminium foil have to be clean before putting them into the recycling.
    </string>
    <string name="info_plastic2">- <b>Plastic bags:</b> they can be reused many times, but when you are finished with them, recycle them in the plastic bins.\n- <b>Bricks or Tetra Pak:</b> packaging used for milk, juice, tomato sauce and more.
        </string>
    <string name="info_paper">- <b>Paper:</b> standard office papers, magazines, newspapers&#8230;\n- <b>Cardboard:</b> cardboard boxes, cereal boxes and the like. Not milk and juice boxes, those go in the plastic bins.\n- <b>Others</b>: comics, paper or cardboard packaging, brochures, envelopes, advertising, paper sheets&#8230;
    </string>
    <string name="info_glass">- <b>Glass:</b> glass bottles, jars and containers. Do not include the metal lids to jars or the bottle caps. Do not throw fluorescents, light bulbs, mirrors, glasses, plates or broken ashtrays. Lightbulbs and such can be dropped off at specific stores.\n- <b>Cosmetics:</b> empty perfume and cosmetic bottles.</string>
    <string name="info_organic">- <b>Organic waste:</b> leftover fruit and vegetables, scraps of meat and fish, shells of eggs, nuts, seafood. Also coffee grounds, teas, matches, sawdust.\n- <b>Dirty paper:</b> you can also deposit dirty kitchen paper, used napkins and oil stained cardboard.</string>
    <string name="info_waste">- <b>Non organic: </b>diapers, pads, tampons, wet wipes, cigarette butts, dust, animal feces, litter sand, hair and pet fur, surgical face masks.</string>
</resources>
